# **Ayush Saxena**

Software Engineer (Angular Developer)

Bareilly, U.P (243001) (+91) 8194083260 saxena.ayush351@gmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a professional Angular developer with around 3 years in various phases of software development life cycle, in implementing business needs, transition and support of existing applications. I am looking for challenging role that allows me to express my full professional potential as an Angular developer

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**HCL Technologies (a research & development Company),** Noida Sector-124 - Software Engineer.

May 2021 – Present

**ErothTech Private Limited (a software development Company),** Noida Sector-125 - Software Engineer.

Oct 2019 - May 2021

**Xenneo Private Limited (a software development Company),** Noida Sector-62 - Angular Trainee.

Jan 2019 – Sept 2019

#### **SKILLS**

Leadership.

Conceptual skills.

HTML and HTML5

CSS and CSS3

Bootstrap3 and Bootstrap4.

Angular 6+

Electron

# **LEARNING EXPERIENCE – Angular**

#### **Boeing (Service Hub) -: Web Application**

The Boeing Company is a multinational corporation that designs, manufactures, and sells airplanes, rotorcraft, rockets, and satellites. In which we managed all the locations,Bin centers, Areas for all the components needed for keeping the tracks for the required parts .

**Technology**: Angular, ATG, Rest API.

Role: Frontend Developer with API Integrations.

#### **BOSL -: Window App**

BOSL is based on Online Software Lottery Which manages & tracks all Customers with Different Modules & Features like (Admin, Distributor, Sub-Distributor) Along with online Payment Functionality.

Technology: Angular, Java, Spring Boot JPA Rest API.

Role: Frontend Developer with API Integrations.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English - can read, write and speak fluently.

Hindi - can read, write and speak fluently.

## **ACCA Online Quiz -: Web Application**

Online Quiz is a simple web application that is just for fun playing online Quiz to increase our knowledge and learn new things.

Technology: Angular 7, Java, Nodejs.

Role: Frontend Developer (Designer, Maintenance & Bug Fix)

# InventisAI -: Web Application

A chatbot service provider website that allows the user to have a chatbot in their project.

Technology: Angular 7, Nodejs, NLP.

Role: Frontend Developer (Designer, Maintenance & Bug Fix)

# **Event-Flix -: Web Application**

Event-Flix is based on Online event management, which manages & Track all events that are created by user with Different Modules & Features like (Admin, Users) Along with online Payment Functionality.

**Technology**: Angular 7, Java, Spring Boot JPA Rest API. **Role:** Frontend Developer with API Integrations.

#### **Curry Leaves-: Web Application**

Curry Leaves is a Specific restaurant app in which users can order their food online and can make online payments.

**Technology**: Angular 7, Java, Spring Boot JPA Rest API.

Role: Frontend Developer with API Integrations.

# **EDUCATION**

**KIET Group of Institutions, Ghaziabad U.P** — *M.C.A* 

Jun 2017 - Jun 2019

DGPA - 7.6

#### Khandelwal College of Management Science and Technology, Bareilly U.P.

— В.С.А

Jun 2014 - May 2017

Percentage – 68%

## **S.R International School,** Bareilly U.P — *Higher Secondary*

Passing year - 2014

Percentage - 64.8%

#### Bishop Conrad School, Bareilly U.P— Matriculation

Passing year - 2012

CGPA - 6.6